&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：为了更好地理解原始值，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: To get a better understanding of how primitive values,
基元类型值，以及一些特殊的值工作，
primitive type values, and some of the special values work,
我们要跳到这个练习中。
we're gonna jump into this exercise.
在本练习中，我们将制作一个多填充。
In this exercise, we're going to make a polyfill.
您将为以下对象定义多边形填充
You're gonna define a polyfill for
这个对象就是我们刚才谈到的实用程序。
that Object.is utility that we just talked about.
所以换句话说，不作弊，
So in other words, no cheating,
您不能去查看它的现有实现。
you can't go look at the existing implementation of it.
您将编写自己的Object.is，这样做时，
You're gonna write your own Object.is, and in so doing,
获得一些处理这些原始值和
get some practice with the idea of dealing with these primitive values and
他们的类型和角落里的箱子之类的东西。
their types and the corner cases and things like that.
所以这里的说明是关于定义Object.is的，
So the instructions here talk about defining an Object.is,
需要两个参数。
it's gotta take two parameters.
记住，它接受两个值作为两个单独的参数。
Remember it takes two values as two separate parameters.
然后，只有当它们完全相同时，才应该返回true。
And then it's supposed to return true only if they're exactly the same thing.
通常情况下，你只需要使用三倍的等号，但是两个主要的角点
Now normally you would just use a triple equals for that, but the two major corner
在三重等于的情况下，它所在的位置是NaN值和负零值。
cases on triple equals where it lies are the NaN value and the negative zero value.
所以你基本上需要解释
So you're gonna essentially need to account for
先是那些，然后如果你不在这些条件中，
those first, and then if you're not in one of those conditions,
然后三重等于会告诉你它们是不是相同的值。
then the triple equals would tell you if they are the same value.
所以这里的说明是关于处理NaN和负零的。
So the instructions here talk about handling the NaN and the negative zero.
您可以使用一个内置的实用程序，如number.isNaN，但是
And you can use a built-in utility like number.isNaN, but
还有一种检查nans的方法不是这样的。
there's also a way of checking for NaNs that isn't that.
看看你能不能弄明白。
See if you can figure that out.
你也可以算出负零。
You can also figure out negative zeros.
最后一点要注意的是，我们正在定义一种多填充材料，
So one last little note here is that we're defining a polyfill,
和多填充图案，正如你在这里看到的，
and the polyfill pattern, as you can see here,
就是你只有在没有定义的情况下才能定义它。
is that you only define something if it's not already defined.
这就是真正的多填充的样子，是不是会有if语句
So that's what a real polyfill would look like, is it would have that if statement
围绕自定义函数的定义进行包装。
wrapped around your definition of your custom function.
这里的挑战是，几乎可以肯定您正在使用JavaScript
The challenge here is that you're almost certainly working in a JavaScript
已经有Object.is的环境，因为那是ES6，所以几年前。
environment that already has Object.is, cuz that was ES6, so years back.
因此，如果您将其包装在if语句中，那么您编写的任何代码都不会
So if you wrap it in an if statement, none of the code you write is ever gonna
运行，您将针对内置的Object.is测试自己。
run and you're just gonna be testing yourself against the built in Object.is.
因此，作为临时攻击，我将禁用if语句。
So as a temporary hack, I would disable that if statement.
您可以通过逐字地说或之类的话来禁用它
You can disable it by literally saying something like or
所以你总是在定义一个。
true so that you're always defining one.
显然，你不会把它留在你正常的多面体里。
You wouldn't leave that in, obviously, in your normal polyfill.
但是为了这个练习的目的，因为你在填充一些东西
But for the purposes of this exercise, since you're polyfilling something
已存在，请确保以某种方式禁用if语句，或者
that already exists, make sure that you disable that if statement in some way, or
您可以只注释掉if语句，好的。
you can just comment out the if statement, okay.
但请记住这一点。
But just keep that in mind.
你将在ex.js中工作。
You're gonna be working in ex.js.
您会注意到，在这个文件中，我有一堆控制台日志语句，并且
You'll notice that in this file I have a bunch of console log statements, and
他们每个人都在断言关于这个测试的一些东西。
each one of them is asserting something about this test.
因此目标是所有这些控制台日志语句都必须
And so the objective is that all of these console log statements all have to
打印为真。
print true.
也就是说，这些调用中的每一个都返回true，并且
That is that each one of these calls all return true, and
这些调用中的每一个都返回false。
each one of these calls all return false.
所以你知道当你拿到所有的真假的时候你有一个合格的测试
So you know you have a passing test when you get all trues and
没有错误打印出来。
no falses printed out.
运行此代码的方式，您可以打开此文件并
The way to run this code, you can open up this file and
从命令行直接在节点中运行它。
run it directly in node from the command line.
您可以将代码复制到控制台中，然后
You could copy your code into a console and
在控制台中运行它，就像在Chrome开发工具中一样。
run it inside of a console, like in your Chrome developer tools.
无论您喜欢如何运行JavaScript，
However you like to run your JavaScript,
不需要任何其他周围的信息。
doesn't need any other surrounding information.
但是你要定义你的对象。是在顶部的PolyFill，并且
But you're gonna define your Object.is polyfill here at the top, and
然后确保它通过了所有测试。
then make sure that it pass all the tests.
这可能需要5到8分钟的时间，所以我们休息一下，
This would probably take someone between five and eight minutes, so we'll break,
让你有一些机会来练习，然后我们会回来
let you have some chances to work on the exercise, and then we'll come back and
谈谈解决方案。
talk about the solution.
如果您获得库存并需要提示，我们将为您提供解决方案，并
If you get stock and you need a hint, the solution is provided for you and
它是ex.fixed.js在同一目录中。
it's ex.fixed.js in that same directory.
好了，祝你在这个练习中玩得开心。
All right, have fun with this exercise.